Andrew Quinn

4929 CSE 2260 Hayward St. Ann Arbor, MI 48105

Email: arquinn@umich.edu Web: web.eecs.umich.edu/~arquinn

Phone: 1.630.453.1899

Introduction

I am a computer science researcher interesting in software systems.

My research proposes new tools, frameworks and algorithms to improve software reliability, focusing largely on improving our ability to debug software. In my thesis, I build new cluster-scale systems to accelerate expensive dynamic program analyses such as dynamic information flow tracking and always-on program invariants. I explored automated systems for debugging persistent memory applications and proposed a new software infrastructure for edge computing.

I am a Microsoft Research Fellow and a National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellow.

EDUCATION

| University of Michigan Ph.D., Computer Science and Engineering | Ann Arbor, MI Sep 2015 - Present |
|--|--------------------------------------|
| University of Michigan M.S., Computer Science and Engineering | Ann Arbor, MI Sep 2015 - May 2015 |
| Denison University B.S., Computer Science and B.A., Mathematics Honors: summa cum laude, Phi Beta Kappa, Deans List | Granville, OH Aug 2010 - May 2014 |
| Fellowships and Awards | |
| Microsoft Research Fellowship Two year fellowship awarded to nine early-career Ph.D. students | 2017 |
| National Science Foundation Graduate Student Research Fellowship Three year fellowship awarded to Ph.D. students | 2017 |
| John L. Gilpatrick Mathematics Award, Denison University Awarded to the most outstanding senior major in the Math and CS department | 2014 |
| Ted Barclay Top Five Student Athlete, Denison University Awarded to the top five student athletes at Denison based on GPA. | 2014 |

Conference Publications

Ian Neal, Ben Reeves, Ben Stoler, Andrew Quinn, Youngjin Kwon, Simon Peter and Baris Kasikci Agamotto: How Persistent is your Persistent Memory Application?. To appear in Proceedings of the 2020 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2020. Acceptance Rate: 70/398 = 17.6%

Andrew Quinn, Jason Flinn, and Michael Cafarella

Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging. In Proceedings of the 2018 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). October 2018. Acceptance Rate: 47/264 = 17.8%

Andrew Quinn, David Devecsery, Peter M. Chen and Jason Flinn

JetStream: Cluster-scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries. In Proceedings of the 2016 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2016. Acceptance Rate: 47/267 = 17.6%

WORKSHOP PUBLICATIONS

Matt Furlong, Andrew Quinn, and Jason Flinn

The case for Determinism on the Edge. In 2nd USENIX Workshop on Hot Topics in Edge Computing (HotEdge). July 2019 Acceptance Rate: 22/39 = 56%

Andrew Quinn, Michael Cafarella, and Jason Flinn

You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding observability with the OmniTable. In Proceedings of the Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS). May 2019 Acceptance Rate: 30/125 = 24%

Presentations

| You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding Observability with the OmniTable | May 2010 |
|--|----------|
| Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS) | May 2019 |

Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI) Oct 2018

JetStream: Cluster-Scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI) Nov 2016

Power Management for Malleable Job Scheduling Denison University department of Math and Computer Science FaST talk Apr 2014

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

| $Ann\ Arbor,\ MI$ |
|---------------------|
| May 2019 - Jun 2019 |
| • |
| Granville, OH |
| Jan 2012 - May 2014 |
| |

PROFESSIONAL SERVICE

| External Review Committee Member Architectural Support for Programming Languages and Operating Systems (ASPLOS) | 2021 |
|---|------|
| Conference Shadow Program Committee Member European Conference on Computer Systems (EuroSys) | 2020 |
| Ph.D. Admissions Committee Member University of Michigan Department of Computer Science and Engineering | 2018 |

Professional Experience

Research Intern mentored by Dr. Suman Nath

| University of Michigan | $Ann\ Arbor,\ MI$ |
|--|--------------------|
| Graduate Student advised by Dr. Jason Flinn and Dr. Peter Chen | Sep 2015 - Present |
| Microsoft Corp. | $Redmond,\ WA$ |

May 2017 - Aug 2017

| International Business Machines (IBM) Software Development Engineer | Dublin, OH Jun 2014 - Aug 2015 |
|---|--|
| Denison University Research assistant mentored by Dr. Jessen Havill | Granville, OH Aug 2013 - May 2014 |
| International Business Machines (IBM) Software Development Engineering Intern | $\begin{array}{c} Dublin,\ OH \\ \text{May 2013 - Aug 2013} \end{array}$ |
| Denison University Research assistant mentored by Dr. Jessen Havill | Granville, OH May 2012 - Aug 2012 |
| Outreach Activities | |
| Discover Engineering, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI | Aug 2019 |
| Techie Club, Georgian Heights Elementary, Columbus, OH | Aug 2014 - Aug 2015 |
| A Call to College, Newark Elementary Schools, Newark, OH | Sep 2012 - Dec 2013 |